Chapter 3: Sumeragi Satsuki

The next day, after their lunch at the mansion, Liselotte brought Rio and Miharu along to visit the royal castle of Galarc. Their goal was, of course, to meet Satsuki before the banquet.

Under normal circumstances, the two of them would have never been allowed inside, but thanks to Liselotte filling out the necessary procedures required at the castle gate, both Rio and Miharu were permitted to enter without investigation.

Once they entered the castle, Liselotte gave a note to one of the castle officials addressed to the king— it requested an urgent audience with King Francois of Galarc. Nobles had the privilege of seeking an audience with the king at any time as long as they had a good reason, and she had exercised that privilege. In some cases, they could be made to wait a month, but this time the official came back with the response that the king could meet them immediately.

However, the information to be discussed must have been deemed to be highly confidential, as they were to use a royal reception room for an unofficial meeting rather than the audience hall for an official one.

Rio, Miharu, and Liselotte were led to the reception room, and Francois soon appeared. Francois was in his late forties, the age where a king was at his pudgiest. His gaze and countenance were stern—typical for a king of great power.

Sandwiching Francois on each side stood a man in his early twenties and a woman in her early teens. They both wore expensive-looking clothes which, combined with their accompanying Francois, implied that they were both royalty. Other attendants wearing maid uniforms made an entrance as well.

“Thank you for coming today. I haven’t met Liselotte face-to-face since I received the report about the attack on Amande. I believed the next time we would meet would be at the banquet, but...” Francois looked at Miharu and Rio. They did not speak, only accepted Francois’ gaze silently while looking down.

“Pardon me. It is a delight to be before Your Majesty. I sincerely apologize for requesting this sudden audience during a time when Your Majesty must be terribly busy with the preparations for the banquet tomorrow. And I am most grateful for your immediate response to my request,” Liselotte said, giving a reverent greeting on behalf of Rio and Miharu.

“It’s not a problem. Even if you had given more advance warning, it wouldn’t have made this any easier to respond to. By bringing the actual person here, you’ve omitted the unnecessary steps in between. Above all, you are very busy yourself. At any rate, let’s all have a seat,” Francois said warmly, then sat down at the head seat. The young man and woman accompanying him sat down on chairs placed in the corner of the room.

“Excuse me.” Liselotte bowed her head and sat down gracefully. Rio and Miharu also bowed once before taking their seats on either side of Liselotte. In contrast to Miharu, whose movements were awkward from nervousness, Rio straightened himself with a downcast look like a noble would.

“...Is this person Miharu? The one who claims to be Satsuki’s friend?” Francois asked.

“This is Sir Haruto. He placed Miharu under his protection when she wandered into this world and requested that I arrange a way for Lady Satsuki to meet her. Furthermore, he assisted in repelling monsters during the attack on Amande, and rescued Princess Flora when she was abducted,” Liselotte explained.

Francois’ eyes widened in interest. “I see, so he’s the enchanted swordsman you mentioned from that incident. I’ve heard of your achievements. You have done your duty well, both with Miharu and the rest. You may raise your head.” In effect, Francois was giving Rio permission to speak to him.

Despite the fact that this was an unofficial meeting, with the other party being the leader of an entire kingdom, stricter rules of etiquette had to be followed than with other nobles. This was why Rio had not lifted his gaze to look directly at Francois’ face. If Rio had joined in on Francois and Liselotte’s conversation, he would have been branded as impolite.

However, once Rio was given permission to speak, he finally opened his mouth. “There is no higher honor than to receive words of praise from Your Majesty.” He raised his head slightly so that Francois could see his face, before lowering it once more.

“It was noted in the report as well, but you really do seem young. To repel a large demi-dragon’s breath with an enchanted sword at that age is quite the feat. I’ve heard that your parents were migrants, but you seem capable of upholding noble etiquette too. What an interesting boy. I would like to hear more about you later.” Francois looked at Rio with great interest. The man and woman in the corner of the room also observed Rio with curiosity in their eyes.

“It would be an honor.” Rio refrained from saying anything more and lowered his head respectfully. Just then, someone knocked on the door to the room before opening it immediately.

“Excuse me.” A girl in her mid teens appeared. She wore what would have been a typical uniform for female knights in this world, only tailored to be more extravagant. However, her facial structure was that of a Japanese person.

She had large eyes and a dignified gaze. Her figure was feminine and slender, and her long hair, which reached down her back, was tied. She was beautiful.

The girl seemed to have run here, as she was slightly out of breath. However, she paid it no mind as she looked around the room anxiously, immediately focusing her gaze on Miharu.

“...Miharu-chan!” the girl — Sumeragi Satsuki — shouted after she’d caught her breath. She’d spoken in Japanese.

“Satsuki-san!” Miharu shot straight to her feet as her face lit up at the sight of her friend. Because Satsuki had spoken in Japanese, Miharu did, too.

Chapter 4: Secret Reunion

Approximately two hours later...

“Your escort has arrived, so let’s get going soon.” Sensing Aishia’s presence, Rio called out to Miharu and Satsuki to signal their departure.

“What escort?” Satsuki tilted her head in confusion.

“I could carry the two of you by myself, but it would be easier with some help, so I called for backup. She’s on the balcony right now — I’m going to open it,” Rio said as he stood up and walked over to the balcony, opening the doors. There stood Aishia alone, wearing a black overcoat.

“...Who’s that?” Satsuki blinked blankly as Aishia came into her view.

“She’s going to help me carry you two. Her name is Aishia, and she’s a good friend of mine,” Rio said.

“Nice to meet you,” Aishia said briefly.

“N-Nice to meet you,” Satsuki replied, captivated by her appearance. She then turned to Miharu. “She’s very pretty and adorable. I’ve never seen anything like it...”

“Yes. I also thought the same when I first met her. Ai-chan is quiet, but she’s a very nice person,” Miharu happily introduced Aishia to Satsuki.

“I would love to get to know you better.” Satsuki glanced at Aishia with a smile.

“Sure,” Aishia nodded.

“What do you want to do? Either Aishia or I will be carrying you, but...” Rio glanced at Aishia as he asked Satsuki.

“Hmm. Could you carry me, Haruto? Aishia can carry Miharu,” Satsuki suggested, looking between Rio and Aishia’s.

“Sure, I’m fine with that. But are you sure you want me to do it?”

“Yup. Miharu gets nervous when she’s around boys, you know? She’d have to cling to you to be carried, but I don’t really mind that kind of stuff. Is that okay with you, Miharu?” Satsuki answered Rio with a laugh, before looking at Miharu.

Miharu nodded after a slight pause. “...Y-Yes, of course. I’m counting on you, Ai-chan.”

“Sure.” Aishia nodded too.

“Then that’s decided. There’s nothing I need to bring, so I’m ready to go anytime,” Satsuki said, walking over to the balcony where Rio and Aishia stood.

“Then I’m going to carry you, now,” Rio said, standing in front of Satsuki.

“Yes, please do,” Satsuki nodded softly.

“If you don’t mind, then...” Rio said, picking Satsuki up in a bridal carry.

“Ah...” Satsuki flinched in surprise at how easily she was lifted up.

“We’re going to fly like this — will you be okay?” Rio asked calmly.

“Y-Yeah. I’m fine, but am I too heavy?” said unsteadily.

“...No, of course not. You’re light,” Rio said with a chuckle, eyes widening. He was surprised at the contrast between the impression he had of her as an articulate and clear-headed woman compared to the girly, innocent side before him.

“Hmph, why are you laughing? I know I said don’t mind this kind of thing, but you don’t really get carried like this at this age, so it’s like... it’s just more embarrassing than I thought it would be!” Satsuki protested with scornful eyes.

“I’m sorry. With my physical body enhanced, it’s easier to carry you this way than piggyback. I can hold onto you properly, so it’s safer,” Rio started explaining, but Satsuki objected to Rio as she pouted her lips.

“I-I know that. It’s not like I was feeling conscious of being like this with you or anything!”

“Okay.” Rio nodded as he broke into a small smile. Meanwhile, Miharu had also been lifted by Aishia and was watching Rio and Satsuki’s exchange closely.

“We’re ready as well,” Aishia declared.

“Let’s go, then. Please hold on tight.” Rio kicked off the balcony floor with a stomp, and his body rose elegantly into the pitch-black sky.

“Uh...” Satsuki instinctively tightened her grip around Rio at the floating sensation she felt.

Am I actually flying? What... What is this? I’m floating? She tried to objectively analyze the gravity-defying phenomenon. However, it wasn’t long until she stopped caring about it entirely. The higher they rose, the smaller the castle below her became, until her vision was filled with nothing but the starry sky.

“Wow! You’re kidding me! It’s so pretty!” Satsuki exclaimed in awe in spite of herself. Her voice could no longer reach the castle below her. “Hey, how amazing is this? Whoa! Look, Haruto! Miharu!” she called out with sparkling eyes. Miharu, flying nearby in Aishia’s arms, watched Satsuki with a smile.

“I’m glad you’re having fun,” Rio said with a smile.

“Yeah, so much fun! I’ve never seen the moon and stars so up close before! I didn’t know they could be so beautiful in this world too. Did you know?” Satsuki asked Rio, beaming innocently at him.

“I did know. Well, I’m not really conscious of it when I’m flying alone, though. I think it’s very pretty today,” Rio replied to his excited passenger with a faint smile.

“I see, so you knew already. Haha, I guess that’s true. You can fly in the sky any time you want. But you’re especially noticing it today, right? Right?” Satsuki accepted his response, laughing happily. She would have been a little sad to hear that she was the only one enjoying the beautiful night sky.

“Are you cold?” Rio asked Satsuki.

“Umm, just a little. There isn’t much air resistance considering how fast we’re flying, so it’s a lot better than being hit directly by the wind...” It was currently summer in the Strahl region, but it cooled down more at night in comparison to Japan. Not to mention, being high in the air made it all the more chilly. Satsuki hadn’t changed into her pajamas, so she was still in her day clothes, but a jacket would’ve been nice.

“I’ll hurry to our meeting place, so please bear with it for a little longer.”

“Yes, please make it an express ride! Ah, it’s so cold.” Satsuki nodded cheerfully and held on tighter to Rio, most likely trying to leech his warmth.

“I’m amazed at Satsuki. She’s already bonded so much with Haruto...” Miharu muttered enviously, at the same time watching Satsuki with a look of admiration.

“You’re doing your best too, Miharu. You’ve been trying to approach Haruto by yourself,” Aishia said to Miharu quietly.

“Do you think so?” Miharu tilted her head a bit doubtfully.

“Yup. You should remain the way you are. Haruto understands your feelings perfectly.” Aishia nodded, then followed after Rio as he quickened his pace a bit.

◇　◇　◇

Several minutes later, the group had flown entirely out of the capital, heading towards a rocky area off the main road. There were no lights, nor any signs of people below them.

“...Hey, how far are we going?” Satsuki asked Rio timidly, feeling slightly spooked.

“We’ve just arrived. I’m going to go down,” Rio said with a huff of laughter, beginning his descent.

“Arrived where? ...Wait, is that it?” Satsuki strained her eyes and looked down, but she couldn’t see very far because the ground was enveloped in darkness. However, she noticed that a faint light had turned on in the darkness.

“Did you notice something?” Rio, slightly wide-eyed, asked Satsuki.

“Yeah. The light of magic essence...”

“I’ve put up a sorcery barrier where we’re about to land. It has a weaker effect from above, but even then, only humans who can detect magic essence can notice the barrier. I guess you’re able to see magic essence.”

“...Yes. I can see it. I’ve heard that the people of this world are typically unable to see it, though,” Satsuki said, staring at Rio’s face in interest.

“This isn’t known among the general public, but you can learn to see it with some special training. Though in your case, it’s probably an effect of the divine arms’ power,” Rio guessed.

“I know I’m not one to speak, being a hero and all, but you’re a pretty extreme oddity,” Satsuki said to Rio with a wry smile. Rio grinned along with her.

Rio touched the surface of the barrier — immediately after, two voices called out for Satsuki. They belonged to, of course, Aki and Masato. Inside the barrier, the residents of the rock house had all lined up in anticipation of their arrival.

Furthermore, Orphia had created a ball of light to levitate in the air, illuminating the inside of the barrier in a way that was invisible to the outside.

“Aki! Masato!” As soon as Satsuki spotted Aki and Masato’s faces, she called their names with a bright grin. Aishia also entered the barrier carrying Miharu, and Rio landed in front of Aki.

“I’m glad that you two seem to be doing well!” Satsuki exclaimed happily.

“You too, Satsuki!”

“I’m so happy you’re okay!”

Masato and Aki ran over to Rio, delighted to be reunited with Satsuki after a long time of being apart.

“Yes, thanks to Rio. I wanted to see you two so much, I asked him to bring me here!”

“I missed you too!” Aki said happily.

Meanwhile, standing a slight distance away was Celia, Sara, Orphia, Alma, and Latifa, all staring at Satsuki with interest; she’d also noticed their presence.

Oh, wow. Aishia was already unbelievably adorable, but these other girls are all something else, aren’t they?? I’d heard he was living together with girls, but with girls like these... Is Haruto collecting pretty faces? Satsuki directed her gaze at the lineup with interest, then looked up at Rio’s face with scornful eyes.

“Umm, yes?” Rio tilted his head in a slightly worried manner.

“...No, it’s nothing.” Satsuki shook her head hesitantly before realizing she was still being bridal carried. She blushed. “Wait, how much longer are you going to carry me for?”

“Umm, I’d love to let you down, but I need you to let go of me first,” Rio said with an amused smile.

“O-Oh, I’m s-sorry!” Satsuki realized she was the one holding onto Rio and released his clothes in a fluster.

“OK, I’m going to let you down, then.” Rio gently placed Satsuki on the ground. Aki and Masato laughed in amusement, watching Satsuki.

“W-What are you laughing at, you two?” Satsuki asked them, blushing in embarrassment.

“Hmph, I’m sensing the arrival of yet another formidable rival,” Latifa muttered, puffing her cheeks up adorably.

“Well, since it’s Rio we’re talking about, it can’t be helped.” Celia pouted her lips a little before giggling softly.

◇　◇　◇

Rio introduced Celia and the others to Satsuki. Celia, Sara, Orphia, and Alma introduced themselves to Satsuki in order, leaving only Latifa.

Incidentally, because of the limited time they had at the stone house, they cut the extra explanations: Celia used her alias, Cecilia, and the others introduced themselves using artifacts to hide their true species.

“I’m Latifa, Onii-chan’s adopted sister,” Latifa said, concisely, to Satsuki.

“Haruto, you have an adopted sister?” Satsuki’s eyes widened slightly.

“Yes. I’m very proud of her. Although I wanted to introduce everyone in more detail, our time tonight is limited. Let’s go inside. The four of you from Earth should spend some time talking,” Rio said, inviting Satsuki into the house.

Satsuki nodded cheerfully, before tilting her head in confusion. “Yeah... Wait, house?” As far as she could see, there was nothing but boulders before her eyes — both inside and outside the barrier.

“It might be hard to tell, but this boulder is a house. The entrance is over there,” Rio explained, looking up at the stone house beside them.

“Oh, I see it now. I thought it was just an oddly large boulder...” When Satsuki spotted the entrance, her eyes widened in wonder. Upon closer inspection, there were window-like sections and benches and ladders placed here and there, showing the area was lived in.

“This way.” Rio guided Satsuki towards the entrance, but Latifa walked there first and opened the wooden door ahead of them.

“Here you go!” Latifa brightly invited Satsuki inside.

“Thanks, Latifa,” Rio and Satsuki said, then one at a time they went inside. Everyone else followed after them.

“Could you please take off your shoes? The shoe box is right over there,” Rio said to Satsuki. Before them was a huge living room.

Incidentally, while the interior looked nothing like Japanese-style architecture, because Rio was the owner of the house and a former Japanese person, everyone made sure to remove their shoes inside. Thanks to that, the inside of the house was clean enough to relax anywhere.

“Wow, it actually functions as a house. It looks even more comfortable than my rooms at the castle... it makes me want to lay on the floor and relax.” Satsuki stood frozen at the entrance, staring at the living room in awe.

“I know, right? I’m living here more comfortably than I was in Japan. Though we don’t have any electronic appliances here,” Masato said earnestly, standing behind Satsuki.

“Oh, wow. I see.” A slightly strained smile appeared on Satsuki’s face.

“Aki, can you show Satsuki to my room? I’m going to go prepare some tea.” Miharu instructed Aki before heading to the kitchen.

“I can prepare the tea, Miharu, so you should go talk with Satsuki, since you have to return in the morning,” Orphia urged.

“...Okay, thank you, Orphia. Follow me then, Satsuki.” Miharu started showing Satsuki the way to her room with Aki and Masato. Rio and the others were left in the living room, and Orphia headed to the kitchen to make tea.

“Professor, there’s something I want to talk to you about. Could we discuss it in my room?” Rio asked Celia.

Celia paused for a second, but replied with a nod. “...Yes, of course. I have something I wanted to discuss too.”

◇　◇　◇

“So, what did you want to talk about?” Once they’d moved to Rio’s room, Celia sat down on the chair that he’d offered to her.

“It’s about the banquet. I heard some information regarding the Beltrum Kingdom, so I wanted you to be aware, just in case.”

“Really?” Celia’s eyes widened quite a bit.

“Yes. You already know that the hero of Duke Huguenot’s faction will be attending, but it seems like the main hero from Beltrum Kingdom will be there too. In other words, the government of the Beltrum Kingdom may come face-to-face with Duke Huguenot’s faction at the banquet.”

“...The current Beltrum Kingdom has been keeping a distance from the Galarc Kingdom, but they aren’t very peaceful with each other. Could they possibly have an underlying diplomatic motive?”

“That, or something could’ve happened within the kingdom itself. Even if that weren’t the case, the heroes from Galarc, Centostella, and Duke Huguenot’s faction will all be in attendance, so there’s the possibility of some kind of military ploy,” Rio explained, listing all the plausible options.

“Something could’ve happened after I ran away. ...No, something could’ve happened because I ran from the wedding. Duke Arbor’s family must’ve lost their honor entirely, making it difficult to control the dissatisfied nobles, or something like that?” Celia’s face clouded with regret as she considered that she might be to blame for causing the drama.

“Even if something did happen, it wasn’t your fault. That is, even if the suspension of your wedding had impacted domestic affairs,” Rio stated firmly.

“Rio...” Celia bit her lip as an indescribable pain ran through her chest.

“If there’s anything you wish to do, please tell me. If there’s anything I can do, please tell me. I’ll make it happen. I took you away from there for this purpose. So please — don’t forget the decision you made at the wedding. Please rely on me.” Rio looked Celia dead in the eye. Before Celia knew it, the pain in her chest had disappeared, replaced with the intense throbbing of her heartbeat.

“O-Okay. Thank you. Right, I remember now. What I felt back then...” Celia smiled bashfully, her cheeks blushing faintly.

I don’t want to cause Rio any trouble. But I’m allowed to, right? I can rely on him, right? She stared right back into Rio’s face.

“Umm, Rio. I... I want to go back home to see my father. That’s why...” Celia mustered up her courage to speak frankly.

“Of course — I’ll accompany you. It will have to be after the banquet ends and everything with Miharu has settled, though...” Rio offered immediately.

“Geez, you’re always so quick to respond. ...But, I’m happy. Thank you. Of course I’m fine with that. Thank you for taking care of me, Rio.” Celia laughed shyly, bowing her head.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, in Miharu’s room, Satsuki was happily spending time together with Miharu, Aki, and Masato. Miharu and Satsuki were sitting down on the bed together, while Aki and Masato sat on chairs.

“When Miharu was put in a different carriage, I honestly thought we were doomed. Aki even started crying,” Masato said, recounting the events that happened right after they wandered into this world.

“W-What?! T-That’s not true!” Aki shouted, embarrassed, in a fluster.

“Liar. You were a mess — throwing a tantrum and wailing like a baby.”

“I said I wasn’t! Anyway, you were so scared, you couldn’t even do anything!”

“Ah, well... I was unarmed back then.”

Masato and Aki were bantering with each other over nothing, like usual. Normally, this would have led into a light siblings’ quarrel, but...

“Heh... hehe... ahaha!” Satsuki started laughing, which made Aki and Masato stop arguing.

“Umm, Satsuki?” Miharu cocked her head.

“Ah, it’s just so funny. Sorry for laughing so suddenly.”

“I mean, it’s fine. What was so funny, though?” Masato asked in confusion.

“It just reminded me of the way you two teased each other when we were still in Japan. It’s been so long since I’ve seen it, I lost my cool for a sec. It was very healing. Aki, Masato... I’m so glad you two are doing well,” Satsuki said.

“Ah, I see.” Masato smiled bashfully.

“Ahaha, normally Takahisa or Miharu would’ve stopped us before it got too heated, though,” Aki said with a sad look, remembering her brother.

“...I still don’t know where Takahisa is, either.” Sensing the change in Aki, Satsuki also spoke with a gloomy look. She had predicted the possibility of him being the hero of Centostella, but she wasn’t certain.

“Right...” Aki bit down on her lip and nodded. Although she already knew that from when Aishia came to inform them of the visit, hearing it again made her heart feel heavy.

“I’ll notify you two as soon as we receive any confirmed information regarding Takahisa. There’s just one thing I want to ask, though. What will you do if he’s discovered?” Satsuki asked. Miharu’s eyes widened in surprise.

“I want to see him, obviously!” Aki replied fiercely.

“Same with you, Masato?” Satsuki checked.

“Well, yeah. If we’re both alive, I’d want to see him,” Masato replied a bit shyly.

“Would you feel the same way even if he belonged to another kingdom as its hero?” Satsuki pressed.

“...Yes.”

“Yeah, I have lots I want to tell him anyways.” Aki and Masato nodded their heads.

“What are you planning to do after you see Takahisa, then? Haruto is taking care of you at the moment, but would you let Takahisa’s kingdom take care of you instead? Of course, if it seems like Galarc Kingdom will treat you well too, you could stay here... Or asking Haruto to keep taking care of you is another choice...” Satsuki asked, digging deeper with her line of questioning.

“We did talk a lot about that before coming here, but...” Aki started somewhat hesitantly.

“You haven’t made a decision yet?”

“...Yeah.”

“I think you understand already, right? That not everyone’s decision may be the same,” Satsuki guessed. Aki’s expression stiffened as if she had hit the nail on the head.

“Well, we had a vague idea it could happen, so we were mindful not to delve too deep into the topic,” Masato said, scratching his head uncomfortably.

Although Rio had been taking care of them until now, there was the possibility they would each live separately from now on, depending on the choices they made.

“It’s fine with me as long as you understand it. Really, I’m probably interfering too much. You’ll know the answer when the time comes, so let’s discuss it when we’re all together,” Satsuki grinned, shrugging her shoulders rather excessively as she looked at Miharu.

“...Okay.” Miharu looked back at Satsuki and nodded apologetically. Meanwhile, Aki was watching Miharu somewhat anxiously.

“Hmm... The topic got all serious, so I’m kind of tired now. We were finally able to reunite with this limited time, so we should use it to talk about more fun topics. Oh, that’s right! Tell me more about this house. It seemed pretty big, so I’d love to have a tour.” Satsuki smiled brightly and changed the topic.

“Hmm... There are a lot of rooms similar to this one, but it might be worth having a look at the gigantic bed in Haruto’s room. I’ve never seen a bed that big before in Japan,” Masato said.

“Wow, so he sleeps in such a big bed all alone?” Satsuki’s eyes widened.

“Well, not really. Latifa and Aishia sleep with him sometimes, which occasionally causes a bit of a commotion...” Aki broke into an amused grin, reminded of those times.

“Wait, he sleeps together with his little sister and Aishia?!” Satsuki exclaimed in surprise.

“The two of them sneak into his bed while he’s sleeping. Cecilia and Sara often find them and scold them about it,” Aki explained with a hint of a wry smile.

“Oh, I see... Well, you can show me that bed later. Are there any other interesting places you can tell me about?” Satsuki grinned happily, having landed upon an interesting piece of information.

“Hmm... The only other place I can think of is the bathtub,” Masato said, cocking his head.

“How nice — a bathtub! I’d love to stretch my arms and legs and take a long, warm bath. The castle has a splendid bathtub too, but the soaps aren’t anything to write home about, and there aren’t any bathtubs like the ones you would see in Japan...” Satsuki’s face lit up as she longingly spoke of Japanese-style bathtubs.

“Do you want to ask Haruto if you can take a bath here, then? We have a bathtub made of stone and a wooden tub as well,” Aki offered.

“Oh, that sounds nice. The perfect combination,” Satsuki responded enthusiastically, her smile pure.

“We also have a nice collection of soaps, so I’m sure you’ll like it,” Miharu added.

“I look forward to seeing that! Wait. Wait, what?! I let my guard down and just went along with the conversation, but... what?! Y-You have one in this house? Really? A Japanese-style bath?” Satsuki had been smiling broadly before she noticed something odd with the conversation. She gasped at Miharu.

“Yes, although it’s more like a hot spring than a Japanese-style bath.” Miharu laughed in amusement.

At that, a fire ignited in Satsuki’s eyes. “Oh my god, a hot spring?” she gulped.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, Rio finished speaking with Celia and returned to the living room. Aishia, Latifa, Sara, Orphia, and Alma were gathered there as well.

“Welcome back, Onii-chan! Did you finish talking? Come — sit down, sit down!” Latifa immediately called Rio to the spot on the sofa between her and Aishia. Aishia shifted to the side, as if reading Latifa’s mind, creating a space for Rio to fit between them.

“Oh, thanks.” Rio sat in the space between them as though this was a natural occurrence. On the other hand, Celia reluctantly lowered herself into the empty one-seater sofa.

“Onii-chan energy — recharge!” Latifa announced, immediately clinging to Rio’s right side.

“Hmph.” The other girls looked bitter, as if they wanted to say something, but it was a little sister’s right to be doted on by her brother, after all.

“Ehehe!” Latifa beamed in satisfaction, enjoying Rio’s attention.

Meanwhile, Aishia didn’t attach herself to Rio as closely as Latifa had, but leaned in enough to toe the line of Celia giving a warning. At times like this, Aishia and Latifa were the only ones that could get this close to Rio, making them extremely formidable.

“Umm, why’s everyone so quiet?” Rio asked, noticing that he was being stared at by Celia, Sara, Orphia and Alma.

Celia sighed in exasperation. “Huh? Isn’t it because we just arrived? What were you guys talking about before?” she asked Sara.

“We were talking about Miharu’s friend, Satsuki. Just wondering what kind of person she is,” Sara answered with a faint smile. At that very moment, the door to Miharu’s room opened to reveal Miharu and Satsuki.

Satsuki’s eyes widened when she spotted Rio sandwiched between Aishia and Latifa, but she called out to him with a grin. “...Hey, Haruto. I have a favor I’d like to ask.” Beside her, Miharu was also giggling in amusement.

“Yes, what is it?” Rio stiffened, feeling a strange presence coming from Satsuki.

“Umm, I’d like to use the bathtub. Is that okay?” Satsuki said with a completely serious expression, clasping her hands together as she pleaded.

“S-Sure. Feel free to help yourself.” The anticlimactic answer drained the strength in Rio’s shoulders, making him agree in relief.

“Really? You’re sure? Thank you!” Satsuki laughed happily.

“It’s just a bathtub — I don’t mind if you use it,” Rio said in amusement, lips turning upwards into a smile.

“What are you saying! When you want to use someone else’s bathtub, it’s only polite to ask the owner of the house for their approval,” Satsuki said, as though she were pointing out the obvious.

“When we told her about the bathtub in this house, Satsuki leaped out the door saying she’d ask you herself,” Miharu giggled.

“That just shows how important that information was to me, gosh.” Satsuki’s cheeks reddened in embarrassment.

“In that case, please ask Miharu about how to use the bathroom,” Rio said.

“Yup. Also, would anyone else like to join us? I’d love to have the chance to talk to everyone.” Satsuki nodded eagerly, turning to address the group of women.

“Us too?” Sara muttered, exchanging a look with Celia and the others.

“Please go enjoy yourselves,” Rio urged them. “Masato and I will wait out here.”

“Ahaha, I should have known... Right...” Masato seemed a little disappointed, laughing bitterly.

“What, did you want to join us too?” Aki shot Masato a dull look, sighing tiredly.

Masato’s face flushed. “N-No! Just go already!”

◇　◇　◇

“It’s so spacious...” Satsuki opened the door to the bathroom and froze in astonishment. The changing room was already large to begin with, and she had nearly yelled “is this a holiday inn?!” when she saw the curtain hanging over the entrance, but none of that could compare to this.

This was definitely a holiday inn. Seeing the bare rock surfaces, artifact-powered bubbling water, and steam filling the entire room had her heart pounding in elation she couldn’t hold back.

“Apparently the water is made through sorcery, but isn’t it just like a hot spring?” Miharu said to Satsuki with a smile, her naked body hidden behind a towel.

“Yeah, this is the best...” Satsuki replied in a daze.

“Come this way — I’ll explain the different soaps and how to use the water.”

“Please do!” Satsuki followed Miharu to the washing area. While it was a little bit cramped with this many people using it all at once, they took turns and compromised with each other’s time. They formed pairs of Miharu and Satsuki, Celia and Latifa, Sara and Alma, and Aishia and Orphia, each helping wash the other’s back.

“Oh, it smells wonderful. If only the bath at the castle had this soap... There’s only a limited amount of hot water, too. Now it feels weird to wonder how a house like this was built in a rocky area in the middle of nowhere.” Satsuki was spellbound by the soap bubbles enveloping her body and sighed at the inadequacy of the castle’s facilities.

“Ahaha, the bathing facilities at the royal castle are meant to be the best in the Strahl region, but once you’ve experienced this house’s bathroom...” Celia said with a smile of exasperation, washing Latifa’s hair beside them.

“Onii-chan made all the soaps in the bathroom, you know!” Latifa added. For the record, Celia’s hair color was still being altered and Latifa still had the accessory-shaped magic artifact to hide her ears and tail.

“I’m shocked... I heard he could cook as well. What can’t Haruto do?” Satsuki said, her eyes widening.

“That’s right, he’s good at pouring tea too. Miharu and Orphia are good as well, so we always have great tea in this house. Snacks, too, of course,” Celia said happily.

“Miharu and Orphia are the ones in charge of making snacks, though. The scones and jam they made last time were something else.” Latifa started drooling at the memory of the taste.

“The more I listen, the more this house sounds like a better place to live in than the castle...” Satsuki said with a small sigh, showing a hint of a bitter smile.

“What’s life normally like living at the castle?” Miharu asked in curiosity, washing the water from Satsuki’s back.

“Well, it’s boring. I wake up in the morning, eat breakfast, study things about this world, eat lunch, exercise a bit to help digestion, study, exercise... By the time I stop, it’s nighttime and another day is over, I guess?” Satsuki described with a dry smile.

“I thought you would’ve interacted with the king and other nobility more, being a hero.” Miharu was a little surprised.

“That was partly out of my own request to be treated as an open secret until the reveal at the banquet, so I haven’t met any nobles yet. Well, I do see the royalty a lot instead, though. You met Michel and Char, right? There are other royals too, but I see those two the most often.”

“Princess Charlotte seemed like a very friendly and carefree person. You’re close to her too, right?”

“Yup. Well, I suppose she’s one of the few friends I’ve made in this world so far. She may seem friendly, but you can’t let your guard down around her.”

“Has it been hard after all? The king seemed like he treated you well, but...” Miharu asked worriedly.

“Yeah, well enough. Outwardly, he’s so nice it’s almost scary, but that’s probably because I have value to him. I let him be nice because I wouldn’t be able to live comfortably otherwise, so in a way, we’re using each other. But I’ve become suspicious that there’s something behind every move he makes, so my biggest worry is my own mental fatigue.” Satsuki smiled in a way that showed exactly that.

That’s why I’d honestly prefer living with Aki and Masato — and, if possible, Miharu — not in a place like that. That’s what I truly feel, but I suppose it won’t work out that way... she thought, sighing quietly.

“If I were to give you advice as the eldest of this house, it would be to make one friend that you can trust from the bottom of your heart — someone you can tell anything to,” Celia said, seeing that she had experience being born and raised in noble society.

“Eh?” Satsuki looked extremely confused.

“...H-Huh? Did I say something weird?” Celia replayed her last words over in her head, wondering if she had said the wrong thing.

“N-No, that’s not it... Umm, this may be impolite of me, but may I ask how old you are, Cecilia? You just said you were the eldest...”

“Umm... T-Twenty-one...” Celia stated in embarrassment.

“...EEEEH?!” Satsuki yelled in great amazement. That attracted the attention of Aki and Sara’s group, who were talking amongst themselves elsewhere.

“How... young...”

“There’s no mistaking that one of them is the young Lady Liselotte, but I wonder which is Lady Satsuki’s friend and which is the savior between the gray-haired boy and black-haired girl?”

“While it isn’t too unusual to bring two women as partners to these events, who would have thought one of the women would be Lady Liselotte... Just what kind of relationship is that?”

“That is also a point of interest... My my, Lady Liselotte aside, the other boy and girl are another remarkable couple and easy on the eyes.”

Liselotte was already deemed to be the most unattainable woman in the Galarc Kingdom, having a reputation as an iron wall of a beauty who had never had any love affairs rumored of her, so for her to appear along with Satsuki’s friend was naturally a huge shock to the nobles.

“...Does anyone know who that boy and girl are?” The nobles asked each other, searching for someone who knew of Rio or Miharu.

“No, I don’t know them.”

“Same here.”

No one knew of the two of them. There was no way anyone would know Miharu, who had been living in the spirit folk village until recently, and Rio’s notable activities started and ended at Amande.

Normally, nobles that entered the hall through the upper floor would proceed to move towards the lower floor, but Rio and the others remained on the upper floor.

“If they’re not coming downstairs, then there might be an explanation of the circumstances later.”

“It makes me even more impatient to see Lady Satsuki.”

The nobles waited in anticipation for what would happen next. They were beginning to gather around Duke Cretia’s family to hear what they had to say, being aware of the situation.

However, the announcement for the next guest arrival began instead.

“The hero, Sir Hiroaki Sakata, Second Princess of Beltrum Kingdom, Princess Flora, eldest daughter of Duke Fontaine, Lady Roanna, and Duke Gustav of the Huguenot family have arrived!” The noble acting as the presenter announced loudly as Hiroaki’s group appeared from the door on the upper floor. In contrast to Hiroaki boldly taking the lead with Flora and Roanna on each side of him as his partners, Duke Huguenot brought up the rear as a supporting role.

For the Huguenot faction, the banquet was the perfect stage to make a public relations show of Hiroaki as the hero belonging to them. Because Hiroaki’s existence wasn’t a secret like Satsuki’s, he had been used widely and proactively in propaganda, but this was the first time he was making an appearance at such a large gathering.

“Her Highness Princess Flora is as beautiful as ever.”

“As expected of Beltrum Kingdom’s top beauty.”

“Lady Roanna is also quite intimidating.”

The nobles naturally focused their attention on Flora and Roanna accompanying Hiroaki as his partners. The two of them followed one step behind Hiroaki as he headed straight for Rio and the others. Flora approached Rio and quietly watched his side profile.

“The hero, Lady Satsuki Sumeragi, His Majesty, and the royal family have arrived!” The hall fell silent in an instant, everyone facing downwards as they waited for their appearance with humble expressions.

Immediately, the door to the upper floor opened slowly, echoing through the silent hall.

“Everyone may raise their heads!” Francois’ words were passed on by the presenting noble. At that, the nobles released their suppressed curiosity and looked up at the floor above them.

There stood Francois alongside Satsuki, surrounded by the members of the royal family. Among them were the First Prince Michel and Second Princess Charlotte.

“Ooh...!” The nobles all raised their voices to cheer at the sight of the Galarc royal family symbolizing their authority. Satsuki’s back was ramrod straight as she asserted her presence, comparable to King Francois’.

Francois raised his right hand. “Thank you for gathering today, everyone. This is a moment to celebrate,” he said from his elevated position on the upper floor. His voice was low and calm, but elegant, and it carried well in the grand space.

“Everyone has gathered here from inside and outside of the kingdom for one reason. As you all know, there is someone I would like to introduce you all to,” Francois said, looking at Satsuki as she stood beside him.

“Allow me to introduce you to the hero that was summoned to the Galarc Kingdom, Lady Satsuki Sumeragi.” Satsuki smiled faintly and grabbed the hem of her dress.

“Oooh!” Cheers echoed throughout the hall.

“Beautiful!”

“What dignity!”

“Truly a goddess among women! As expected of a hero!”

Voices praising Satsuki could be heard from every corner of the hall. The male nobles were particularly excited at how much sweeter her appearance was than they’d expected. There were even some throwing exaggerated comments around.

“Hmm.” Seeing the venue react to Satsuki’s figure with songs of praise made Hiroaki frown slightly in displeasure. Beside him, Roanna noticed Hiroaki’s slight change in demeanor.

“Sir Hiroaki, is something the matter?” she whispered in his ear.

“Nothing, I just thought they’re being a bit over the top. The hall is more interested in Satsuki than they were with me,” Hiroaki said, looking down at the hall below him.

“What are you saying? The spotlight is just temporarily shifted to her because this is her first public appearance, and everyone is curious. Everyone here is just as expectant and attentive to you as well, Sir Hiroaki,” Roanna said with a smile.

“Ah, well, if you say so, then perhaps... I personally don’t want to be in the spotlight, though...” Hiroaki said with an exasperated and bitter smile. However, contrary to his words, his expression said that he was more than willing to play the part of a hero.

“Well, weren’t you talking so passionately about how you would save us before? There’ll be no going back once we formally declare your position at this banquet,” Roanna said with a cheeky smile and uneasiness nonetheless.

“Hey hey, don’t make that face. I promised you, didn’t I? That I would be the one to protect you and Flora. Well, a man doesn’t go back on his words,” he said with a small, awkward shrug. His desire to protect others seemed to be stimulated.

“In that case, I will continue to serve at your side with what little power I have,” Roanna declared resolutely.

Ah, at first I wanted to become a carefree adventurer and form my own harem, but now it seems like I have no other choice than to be a hero. The noble class girls are cute, and above all, devoted. There’s no guarantee I’d meet women as fine as this if I became an adventurer, too. I guess the hero route ain’t that bad, then. Hiroaki directed a smile at Roanna with a huff before looking back on how his own change of heart and letting out a heavy sigh.

“Silence! You are before His Majesty!” The noble presenter’s voice echoed loudly, seeing the commotion in the hall. The tumult came to a stop, cutting off Hiroaki and Roanna’s conversation too.

“It is fine. Everyone’s cheers are most understandable,” Francois stated in a cheerful mood. “It has indeed been over a thousand years since the Strahl region was last graced with heroes. Perhaps this is a sign of prosperity from the Six Wise Gods. At any rate, there is good news to be shared tonight. Many of you may be aware, but there is another hero in our presence. The hero, Sir Sakata Hiroaki, Princess Flora Beltrum, and Duke Huguenot. Step this way,” Francois said, and Roanna remained where she was.

Hiroaki nodded a bit nervously before walking forward. Things were progressing as they had discussed in advance, but he had never been in the spotlight before so many people while he was living on Earth. It was no surprise that he was a bundle of nerves.

“Beltrum Kingdom’s Second Princess, Princess Flora, and the well-renowned Duke Huguenot have an important announcement to make. Everyone, listen carefully,” Francois said, stepping back. Duke Huguenot assumed his place and looked down at the nobles in the hall. He gave a reverent bow.

“As introduced just now, I am Gustav Huguenot. As His Majesty King Francois stated, we wish to borrow this space today to make an extremely important announcement to the people of the Galarc Kingdom. As you all know, the Kingdom of Beltrum was divided internally into two factions of nobility after the occupancy by the Proxia Empire at one of our military bases. One of them is the faction led by Duke Arbor, currently using the royal capital as their base, and has real power over all things by using His Majesty King Philip as a puppet,” he began, speaking openly and eloquently.

The nobles in attendance silently lended their ears towards Duke Huguenot’s words.

“Inexperienced as I am, the faction I lead is formed of those who were unfortunately driven out by Duke Arbor’s purification activities, barely escaping to Rodania alive. Outwardly, the reason for Duke Arbor’s purification activities was the denouncement of one of the military bases being occupied by the Proxia Empire. However, we possess evidence that Duke Arbor has been colluding with the Proxia Empire for some time.”

The hall stirred a little. It was an unspoken agreement shared within the Huguenot faction, but this was the first time they were declaring their stance in a public setting.

“Unfortunately, it isn’t conclusive proof, but in regards to the occupation — no, cession of territory to the Proxia Empire, we suspect with near certainty that Duke Arbor exchanged some form of secret agreement. In reality, the faction that formerly asserted a hard line towards the Proxia Empire has, whether they hold true power or not, completely changed their attitude towards them and formed an alliance. At the same time, they have completely distanced themselves from the Galarc Kingdom,” Duke Huguenot said, skillfully mixing conjecture with facts into his speech to present a convincing argument.

“...” No one in the hall showed any particular negative attitude to Duke Huguenot’s speech, the plausibility hanging in the air.

“However, the current distance between the Beltrum Kingdom’s current administration and the Galarc Kingdom is not the desire of our beloved King Philip. As I mentioned before, His Majesty has been made a puppet of the treacherous Arbors. Anyone who makes light of the royal authority bestowed by the Six Wise Gods should not be overlooked. Her Highness, Princess Flora, is also aware of the situation His Majesty has been placed in and greatly laments the current state of things,” Duke Huguenot said with a regretful expression, stressing his point with a look at Flora standing beside him. The audience in the hall gulped and listened intently regardless of their own nationality.

“Thus, I have taken Her Highness under my own protection. On top of that, a base has been established in Rodania to recruit like-minded individuals who cannot accept Arbor’s misgovernment. Our goal is to hand over the power of the kingdom to the rightful ruler with the royal bloodline and restore Beltrum to its former glory. In other words, we have stood up for the great cause of restoring the Beltrum Kingdom to its rightful monarchy. Princess Flora is a symbol of that. That is why I am declaring, here and now: with Her Highness Princess Flora as the representative, we are forming the Beltrum Kingdom Special Administration, named Restoration.” Duke Huguenot grandly declared the formation of a new organization, looking at Flora and the Galarc Kingdom King Francois behind him.

Francois stood in line with Flora and Duke Huguenot and officially approved of the formation of Restoration as witness. “I hereby declare that the Galarc Kingdom recognizes the formal establishment of the Beltrum Special Administration, Restoration.”

“Ooh...!” The nobles in the hall made a great stir. Until now, Duke Huguenot’s faction had been in an unofficial position, but there was great meaning in forming an official organization and having a large kingdom’s recognition.

“Furthermore, Sir Hiroaki Sakata, the hero summoned by the divine stone, has also acknowledged the formation of Restoration and given his firm promise to assist us in our activities,” Duke Huguenot added, motioning towards Hiroaki. Hiroaki raised his right hand with a smirk, and the venue broke into cheers.

“As stated before, the representative of the organization will be Her Highness Princess Flora, but Sir Hiroaki will also be formally affiliated with Restoration. By their leave, I will be acting as an advisor to the two.” At this moment, Duke Huguenot’s face was that of a man that had regained his glory, as he spoke with true eloquence. Hiroaki was also riding the high. Having heard the cheers echoing throughout the hall, his mouth was turned into a truly pleased smile.

...So this situation is exactly what Duke Huguenot planned, huh... The hero from the Beltrum government will arrive tomorrow. Looks like I’ll have more things to report to the Professor, Rio thought, looking on at Duke Huguenot and Hiroaki’s confident smiles.

If the hero, Sakata Hiroaki, hadn’t descended upon them, the Huguenot faction would never have managed to form the Restoration so smoothly. Even with the backing of the Second Princess and the possession of the divine stone, it was doubtful that that would have been enough to put them back into the spotlight once more.

However, whether it was by coincidence or inevitability, Sakata Hiroaki appeared before the Huguenot faction.

The general public was a mass of simple creatures. Even though they had the same role in personifying the authority of the Six Wise Gods, a disciple as the personification was thankfully easier to understand than a divine item like the sacred stone.

As a result, Duke Huguenot obtained two hands in the form of the Second Princess and the hero, gained the backing of the large Galarc Kingdom, and managed to form the Restoration successfully.

For the current Beltrum Kingdom, where the power of the crown had weakened, the aim of regaining the glory of the past sounded like nonsense, but a just cause was required.

Though he had been handed a blessing, Duke Huguenot’s overall capabilities were truly magnificent. The current situation was proof of that.

Fortune is finally in my favor. Haruto... While it is unfortunate that he’s forming a closer relationship with the Galarc Kingdom, I suppose that cannot be helped. Duke Huguenot glanced at Rio, smiling at the cheers of the venue.

Francois raised his right hand high to silence the venue. “Furthermore, with the establishment of the Restoration, our Galarc hero Lady Satsuki Sumeragi will be officially forming an alliance with the Restoration along with Sir Hiroaki Sakata. I hereby recognize this as fact.

“Our future, as we walk alongside these two heroes, disciples of the Six Wise Gods, will surely be bright. That is why I ask the two heroes: will you follow us along our path?” He asked Satsuki and Hiroaki in an exaggerated manner.

“Yes. As long as you walk the righteous path, I, Satsuki Sumeragi, promise to assist your kingdom with my humble power,” Satsuki answered smoothly with the script prepared in advance. Because she had plenty of experience standing in front of others as a member of the student council in high school, she was used to the gazes of the people before her and didn’t seem nervous. Applause rang through the hall.

Then, the gazes of the audience gathered on Hiroaki next.

Ah, if they’re asking for a favor they should really watch their wording. Kings are so full of themselves — I can’t stand it, Hiroaki thought to himself. Perhaps because of the position as king, Francois’ pompous speech touched upon his nerves. Hiroaki hated being looked down on. However —

“Ah, sure. I vow to assist you as long as your actions are righteous,” Hiroaki nodded calmly and said.

Well, it’d be more generous of me to respond calmly here, he thought to himself. Applause welcoming Hiroaki’s vow resounded loudly.

“That is all. Now, you may all enjoy tonight’s banquet as you please. Or so I would like to say, but first, I have a few people to introduce. As was said before, this is Lady Miharu, a friend of Lady Satsuki, and her savior Haruto. The two of you, come forth,” Francois said, calling Rio and Miharu over.

“Yes, Your Majesty.” Rio bowed his head respectfully. Meanwhile, Miharu replied with stiff fear.

“Y-Yes.”

“This elegant girl is Lady Miharu Ayase. Though she was summoned here from the same world as Lady Satsuki, she found herself in a deserted grassland instead of the royal castle. The one who protected Lady Miharu and brought her to the castle was this young man — Haruto. You may have heard of how Amande was under the attack of monsters just recently. There were harmful creatures such as demi-dragons among them, but Haruto drove them away with his enchanted sword. It was on that occasion that he rescued Princess Flora and formed a friendship with Liselotte. Though he is a wandering swordsman traveling through the lands, he is another hero in his own right. Do make sure that you do not underestimate him for being a commoner and show impoliteness,” Francois said, praising Rio greatly while strongly warning the nobles away from acting rude. The nobles who listened to the king’s direct statement of his heroism stirred noisily.

Liselotte smiled proudly as the audience looked to her. Most of the nobility at the venue quietly decided to treat Rio as their superior that night, beating the name Haruto into their heads.

“That is all. This time, you may all enjoy the banquet for real,” Francois said, finally signaling the official start of the banquet.

◇　◇　◇

Afterward, Rio, Miharu, and Liselotte joined up with Satsuki, Francois, and the other royals to receive the surge of nobility that came climbing up the stairs from the hall. Although the conversations were short and only involved a simple greeting exchange, there were a great number of people to get through, unfortunately.

Rio formed a group with Miharu, Liselotte, and Charlotte separate from Francois or Satsuki beside them, but many people came to greet Satsuki — who was, of course, the guest of honor — as well as her friend Miharu. Rio, who’d been directly introduced by Francois as a hero, was also a point of interest.

The guests included great lords such as Duke Gregory and Duke Valier, father of George’s fiancee Colette, and while conversation with royalty and nobility was tiring for the inexperienced, Liselotte and Charlotte skillfully offered their banquet experience and support to lessen the burden on the others.

Nevertheless, greeting the guests took one to three minutes each, so although the thousands of nobility hadn’t come one by one, they had to repeat the same greetings at least a hundred times. Thus, even with short breaks in between, the time added up until Rio and the others had conversed with the nobility for nearly four hours. As a result, by the time they were done greeting most of the nobility, it was nearly time for the banquet to wrap up.

“Would anyone like a refreshment?” A waitress carried around drinks within gold goblets which Miharu and Rio, who was also fatigued for once, accepted.

“...Yes, I’ll take one.” Gulping down the well-iced cocktail, their throats were quenched in an instant. At the same time, a huge wave of fatigue came upon them.

Charlotte gulped down her drink before expressing her appreciation towards Rio and Miharu with a smile. “Thank you for your hard work today, Sir Haruto. Lady Miharu.”

“Yes, even I feel a little tired,” said Rio.

“We’ll be ending tonight’s event soon, but I think you should have an idea as to why the banquet takes place over three days. The first day always ends after greeting everyone you don’t normally see, so we limit the attendees to those within our circles and prepare for outside guests on the second and third day. You two must have been especially busy, as the banquet ends with just the greetings for us royalty and guests of honor. I’m sorry for that,” Charlotte explained, holding a hand against her cheek as she apologized to Rio and Miharu. Seeing how the members of the Restoration were permitted to attend the first day, it showed just how much special treatment they were receiving.

“Not at all. We’re the ones causing trouble with our abrupt attendance, so please make use of us whenever you need to,” Rio said willingly.

“Yes, I’ll do my best as well!” Miharu agreed.

“However, position-wise, the first day is probably the toughest day for you two. You’ve already finished greeting the nobility from the Galarc Kingdom and Restoration tonight, and there’ll be other heroes in attendance from the second day onwards, which will scatter everyone’s attention. You should have a little bit of time to move around freely tomorrow,” Liselotte added.

“Yes, it’s our job as royalty to greet important figures from the other kingdoms. Please relax and enjoy yourselves tomorrow. Would you like to join the dance? If there’s time to spare, I’d love to have Sir Haruto as my partner for a song,” Charlotte said, inviting Rio with a flirtatious look.

Normally, the unspoken rule was for the man to make the invitation for a dance, but it was also acceptable for the woman to do the asking, depending on their relationship. For such exceptional cases, it was considered a breach of manners for an unmarried man to decline a dance invitation from an unmarried woman.

All the more so for Rio, who despite being Miharu’s savior, was still merely a commoner. There was no way he could decline. Or rather, there would be disadvantages in declining the offer, whereas there wouldn’t be any in accepting.

“Yes, it would be my honor,” Rio agreed without hesitation.

“Oh, I’m happy to hear that. In that case, it’s a promise — please ask me out tomorrow, Sir Haruto,” Charlotte said, grasping Rio’s arm as she drew closer to him.

“...Yes.” Rio almost stiffened up by impulse, but nodded amiably. He suddenly looked around to gauge the reactions of their surroundings, and Miharu startled in unrest. Liselotte sighed quietly so that Rio wouldn’t hear.

“Well then, I shall head over to Father’s side for a while. It looks like Lady Satsuki is heading this way now, so please continue your conversation.” Charlotte glanced at Miharu and smiled, bowing gracefully before looking in the direction of King Francois. Satsuki had just finished her wave of greetings and was left free to make her way towards them.

Charlotte grasped the hem of her dress and elegantly bowed to Rio and the others before calling out to Satsuki, who was about to replace her spot. “Thank you for your hard work, Lady Satsuki. I’m going to head over to Father, so please enjoy what little time is left in Sir Haruto’s company.”

“Yup, thank you. Good work today, Char.” After Satsuki smiled and nodded, Charlotte headed over to Francois. “Great job today, you three. Thank you for staying right beside these two for the whole time, Liselotte. I felt reassured,” Satsuki said to Rio, Miharu, and Liselotte.

“Not at all. Her Highness Princess Charlotte was present as well, and these two were answering all inquiries very smoothly without my assistance.” Liselotte shook her head with a smile.

“That’s not true. It was a big help to have you there,” Miharu said, and Rio agreed.

“What they said. And besides, I wanted to thank you for bringing Miharu to the banquet in the first place, Liselotte,” Satsuki said.

“I brought Lady Miharu to the banquet because I owed Sir Haruto a debt. If anything, bringing Lady Satsuki’s friend here has ultimately benefited me as well, so I should be the grateful one. I’ve been able to form a new bond with Sir Haruto as well,” Liselotte smirked devilishly and glanced at Rio. The four people present could tell what kind of relationship she meant without any further detail.

“I’ve heard that you have memories of your previous life, including the story behind the Ricca Guild. Of course, I don’t know the specific details of your past life...” Satsuki said as she carefully watched Rio and Liselotte’s reactions. She could only imagine herself what it was like to have memories of a past life, but she figured the topic of a dead person’s memories was rather delicate and found it hard to ask about it directly.

That being said, it was the perfect topic to dig into how close the relationship was between Rio and Liselotte, and depending on what was discussed, it could give her a clearer view of Liselotte as a person. With the four of them gathered together, it was the optimal timing to bring up the topic, even in a roundabout way.

“Actually, while part of the reason is due to how I’ve been too busy to make the time, we haven’t really sat down and discussed our past lives with each other in detail,” Liselotte said with a wry smile, glancing at Rio.

“It could also be because of the difficult topic,” Rio added with a slightly guilty look. As a matter of fact, the reason why Liselotte hadn’t discussed her past life in great detail was due to Rio hinting at his connection to Miharu in his previous life — he’d requested that he be the one to tell Miharu and the others the truth about how Miharu was from a world four years before Haruto and Rikka died.

Until Rio told Miharu the truth, she wouldn’t say anything. She drew a line there out of consideration for Rio, which he was somewhat aware of.

“Yes. However, I’ve wanted to talk to you too. If it’s okay with Sir Haruto, I would like to discuss this more in the future,” Liselotte said.

“...After the third night of the banquet, sometime in the near future, I’d like to have some of your time to discuss it,” Rio declared to Liselotte eloquently.

“Is that really okay with you?” Liselotte widened her eyes a bit and looked at Rio.

“Yes. My goal was this banquet to begin with. I won’t put it off anymore,” Rio said, showing a fleeting smile. Incidentally, the goal he was referring to was his deadline to reveal the truth to Miharu and the others. However, Miharu and Satsuki had no idea what he was talking about, and tilted their heads in confusion.

“...I see. Well then, I’ll be looking forward to it. There’s a lot of things I want to talk about with you,” Liselotte rejoiced with a kind smile.

“It seems like these two are lost in their own world. Right, Miharu?” Satsuki narrowed her eyes at Rio and stepped closer to Miharu, who was similarly being left out of the conversation. Miharu looked panicked and stumbled over her words.

“Ah, no... Umm...”

“Don’t worry. I’ll be sure to tell you as well, Satsuki.” Rio said with a bitter smile.

“Hmm, I don’t intend on prying into things forcefully...” Satsuki had an apologetic but conflicted look on her face.

“It’s something relevant to you too.”

“...Hmm. Well, all right then.” At Rio’s words, Satsuki’s eyes widened as she nodded. Meanwhile, Miharu was silently and idly watching Rio, when their gazes suddenly met.

“Of course, I’ll tell Miharu too. I’ve stayed silent about it until now, and I know it’s completely at my convenience to tell you now... But I’d appreciate it if you could listen,” Rio explained awkwardly, frowning at Miharu.

“O-Okay...” Miharu gulped, nodding her head.

“...It feels like the air got a bit heavy. Okay! Let’s set this conversation aside for now. Oh yes, that’s right. Liselotte, there’s something I’ve always wanted to ask you in person.” Satsuki clapped her hands together as she changed the subject, looking at Liselotte.

“Sure, what is it?” Liselotte cocked her head.

“Does the Ricca Guild handle rice and miso?” Satsuki asked, looking at Liselotte’s face expectantly.

“Ah, of course you would miss that,” Liselotte seemed to sense Satsuki’s emotions and laughed a bit sadly in empathy.

Satsuki assumed there was little hope from Liselotte’s reaction. “I guess you don’t have it, then...?” she asked helplessly.

“Technically speaking, we do have rice. However, we lack an appropriate method to cook the rice grains into white rice. I eat it as risotto, but I do miss the taste of white rice. Unfortunately, I don’t have the knowledge of how to produce miso, so it doesn’t exist at present,” Liselotte replied regretfully.

“I see. I asked around in the castle, but they said they didn’t know, so I didn’t have high hopes... Ah, I want to eat white rice and miso soup...”

“...Yes, I want to eat it too.”

Meanwhile, Rio and Miharu exchanged a slightly awkward glance with each other, unsure of how to react when they had been eating that on a daily basis. Rio realized it would be bad to stay silent and spoke up to the two of them. “...In that case, shall I prepare it for you?”

“...Huh?” Satsuki and Liselotte both widened their eyes, looking at Rio in unison.

“I have rice and miso, so I can share some with you. And with some pickled vegetables too, if you’d like,” Rio said with a strangely strained smile as he explained his previous statement in more detail.

“Y-You have them?!”

“And with pickled vegetables?!”

Satsuki and Liselotte reacted in unison once more, drawing close to Rio.

“Well, yes, actually...” Rio nodded awkwardly.

“You! If you had them you should have said so earlier!”

“That’s right! Do you know how long I’ve spent searching for those?!”

Satsuki and Liselotte were completely synchronized in their pouting. Even the normally courteous and well-spoken Liselotte was showing her true self at the prospect of a white rice, miso soup, and pickled vegetables set.

“I-I understand. Then, sometime in the near future, if you could find the time to have a meal with just the four of us. I would be happy to prepare the food.” Rio was overwhelmed by their enthusiasm and made a firm promise, though he left all the minor details to them.

“A meal with the four of us... No, I got it. It’s for the sake of rice and miso soup and pickled vegetables. I’ll negotiate a way to hold a dinner party in my quarters.” Satsuki hummed in thought, refusing to back down.

“Please do, Lady Satsuki,” Liselotte said with a serious expression.

The first night of the banquet came to an end, and they all fell into a deep sleep, too tired to visit the stone house.